Kids?
孩子们？
Anybody home?
有人在家吗？
Anybody?
有人吗？
Okay, new Goldie. This is your home.
好的，新来的Goldie。这是你的家。
Full disclosure:
完全坦白：
something bad did happen to the previous tenant.
前一任租客确实遭遇了不好的事情。
There we go.
好了。
[kids chattering indistinctly]
[孩子们含糊不清地聊天]
- Hi, Dad. - Nothing!
- 嗨，爸爸。 - 没什么！
What's in your hand?
你手里拿着什么？
[scoffs] Like I said, nothing.
就像我说的，什么都没有。
What about the other hand?
另一只手呢？
[clears throat]
（清嗓子）
Nada.
没有。
I'm sold.
我信了。
Let's see both hands.
让我们看看两只手。
Hey, Dad, jazz hands!
嘿，爸爸，爵士手！
[screaming]
（尖叫）
Aah!
啊！
Jazz hands! I always fall for jazz hands.
爵士手！我总是被爵士手骗到。
- Goldie?
Goldie?
- Uh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no.
呃，不。不，不，不，不，不，不。
This is Goldie.
这是Goldie。
Why is he in a bag?
他为什么在袋子里？
I was just taking him for a walk.
我刚才正带他去散步。
He likes to see the koi pond at the mall.
他喜欢看商场的锦鲤池。
Dad.
爸爸。
Okay, I like to see the koi pond at the mall.
好吧，我喜欢看商场的锦鲤池。
Dad!
爸爸！
[sighs] Fine.
（叹气）好吧。
Listen, sweetie, I have to tell you something.
听着，宝贝，我得告诉你一件事。
[clears throat]
（清嗓子）
Goldie swam his last lap, kiddo.
Goldie游完了他的最后一圈，孩子。
And I didn't want to upset you,
我不想让你难过，
so I was just trying to replace him before you got home.
所以我试着在你回家之前把他替换掉。
So Goldie's really gone?
所以Goldie真的走了？
I forget.
我忘了。
Is this Goldie #7 or Goldie #8?
这是Goldie #7还是Goldie #8？
W-w-wait. Goldie's been gone before?
等等。Goldie之前就离开过吗？
Seven times?
七次？
Oh, right.
哦，对了。
We're not supposed to tell Dawn
我们不应该告诉Dawn
about all the fish that we flushed.
关于我们冲走的那些鱼。
- W-w-w-wait.
等等。
You guys all knew about this?
你们都知道这件事？
Since when?
从什么时候开始的？
Since Goldie #3.
从Goldie #3开始。
Remember her?
记得她吗？
[all sighing]
[大家都叹气]
I cannot believe you guys.
我真不敢相信你们。
How could you keep this a secret from me?
你怎么能对我保密呢？
'Cause we didn't want you to feel bad.
因为我们不想让你感到难过。
And now you feel bad.
现在你感到难过了。
So we were right.
所以我们是对的。
At least we have Goldie #8, who'll live forever!
至少我们还有Goldie #8，她会永远活着！
Uh, Dad...
呃，爸爸...
We've got a floater.
我们有个漂浮物。
He never even got to see the koi pond.
他甚至都没能看到锦鲤池。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[rhythmic clapping] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[laughter]
笑声
What are you chuckleheads laughing about?
你们这些傻瓜在笑什么？
Let me guess.
让我猜猜。
It's a secret and you can't tell me.
这是个秘密，你不能告诉我。
Oh, no, it's not a secret.
哦，不，这不是秘密。
We were just laughing about how you didn't know
我们只是在笑你不知道
about all those replacement Goldies!
那些替代的Goldies！
[boys laughing]
[男孩们笑]
I guess you had to be there.
我想你得在场。
And not be you.
而且不是你。
Hey, quadalupes.
嘿，四足兽。
Since we had some problems with Goldies 1 through 8,
由于Goldies 1到8出现了一些问题，
I'd like you to meet, Mike.
我想向你们介绍，Mike。
Mike?
Mike？
I don't know if Mike's a bird name.
我不确定Mike是不是鸟的名字。
- [squawking] Mike's a bird name.
- [咯咯叫] Mike是鸟的名字。
See?
看吧？
Sweet! He talks.
太棒了！他会说话。
- Doodie. - Doodie.
- 便便。 - 便便。
[laughs] He said doodie.
[笑] 他说便便。
So is this the original Mike or Mike #2?
那么这是最初的Mike还是Mike #2？
- [squawks] Number two.
- [squawks] 二号。
[laughs] He said number two.
[laughs] 他说二号。
We should've gotten this bird six fish ago.
我们早该在六条鱼之前就买这只鸟。
- Tom, you said you were going to get a new fish.
- 汤姆，你说过你会买一条新鱼的。
Why does Goldie #9 have feathers?
为什么第九号金鱼有羽毛？
And a beak?
还有喙？
And is not a fish?
而且不是鱼？
His name is Mike, and before you say anything negative, you should know that I can't get my money back.
它叫迈克，在你说任何负面的话之前，你应该知道我无法退款。
Well, Mike is not staying in our house.
好吧，迈克不能留在我们家。
- [squawks] Pretty lady, pretty lady.
- [squawks] 漂亮女士，漂亮女士。
Oh. But Michael can.
哦，但迈克尔可以。
- Are these part of your new clothing line, Mom?
——这些是你新服装系列的一部分吗，妈妈？
They're awesome.
它们太棒了。
Thanks. You kids inspired me.
谢谢。你们这些孩子给了我灵感。
You wear out your clothes so quickly I wanted to make
你们衣服穿得那么快，我想做些
something that could stand up to the quadnado.
能经得起旋风的东西。
Ooh, I'm calling it...
哦，我要给它起个名字……
HarperArmor.
哈珀盔甲。
I can't wait to rock it at the fashion show.
我迫不及待要在时装秀上展示它了。
What fashion show?
什么时装秀？
Mom's having a fashion show.
妈妈要举办一场时装秀。
She is?
真的吗？
And we're going to be the models.
而且我们将会是模特。
We are?
我们吗？
We totally talked about this at the sundae bar.
我们在圣代吧那里完全讨论过这个。
Whoa, whoa, wait. Sundae bar?
哇，哇，等等。圣代吧？
Yeah, Dad always gets it for us after we lose a goldfish.
是啊，每次我们失去一条金鱼后，爸爸总是会带我们去那里。
all: Oh.
哦。
So we're going to be models.
所以我们将会是模特。
Some of us.
我们中的一些人。
They're children's clothes, Tom.
那是儿童服装，汤姆。
I'm just saying.
我只是说说而已。
I'm no stranger to the modeling game, man.
我对模特行业并不陌生，伙计。
You were a foot model, Tom.
你是个脚模，汤姆。
A "before" foot model.
是“之前”的脚模。
My toe fungus paid for the power windows in your minivan.
我的脚气病还帮你付了面包车的电动车窗钱呢。
And I can still bring the heat to the catwalk.
我依然能在T台上散发魅力。
Check out my sizzle.
看看我的风采。
Judging by that walk, I think his fungus is back.
从那步伐看，我觉得他的脚气又回来了。
I heard that.
我听到了。
So...a goldfish and a fashion show?
所以...金鱼和时装秀？
Anything else I don't know?
还有我不知道的事吗？
Ooh, you forgot about the sundae bar.
哦，你忘了圣代吧。
What happened to us?
我们怎么了？
We never had secrets from each other.
我们从不互相隐瞒。
We used to have a circle of trust,
我们曾经有一个信任圈，
but now that's broken.
但现在那已经破裂了。
What we need is a quadfession session.
我们需要的是一个四重坦白会。
What's a quadfession session?
什么是四重坦白会？
- All right, boys.
好了，男孩们。
The quadfession session has officially begun.
四方坦白大会正式开始。
Still don't know what it is.
我还是不知道这是什么。
If we're going to trust each other
如果我们打算互相信任
we need to wipe the slate clean and start over.
我们需要从头开始，把过去的一切都抹掉。
So we need to confess our deepest, darkest secrets.
所以我们需要坦白我们最深、最黑暗的秘密。
That'll make us even and rebuild the circle of trust.
这样我们才能扯平，重建信任的圈子。
This is a waste of time.
这是在浪费时间。
We don't keep secrets from each other.
我们之间没有秘密。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
Every night at dinner, when you're not looking,
每天晚餐时，当你不注意的时候，
Dicky takes a sip of your milk.
迪基喝了你的牛奶。
But you know I don't like sharing glassware!
但你知道我不喜欢共用玻璃杯！
And that's why he does it. He thinks it's funny.
这就是他这么做的原因。他认为这很有趣。
And it is.
确实有趣。
Yeah, well, Ricky, remember when you "lost" your lucky ruler?
是啊，瑞奇，记得你“丢失”的那把幸运尺子吗？
Leonardo Da Inchy?
达·因奇？
Well, he's not lost.
它其实没丢。
- Dicky threw him away. - What?
- 迪基把它扔了。 - 什么？
I tried to measure my tongue and threw up on it.
我试着量我的舌头，结果吐在上面了。
Doesn't feel good to be lied to, does it, Ricky?
被欺骗的感觉不好受吧，瑞奇？
No.
没有。
That's why we need this.
这就是我们需要这个的原因。
So don't hold back.
所以不要保留。
What's said in the circle stays in the circle.
圈子里说的话留在圈子里。
Trust each other.
相互信任。
Nicky, you're up.
尼基，轮到你了。
Okay...
好的...
As you all know,
众所周知，
I have a very deep bellybutton.
我有一个非常深的肚脐。
Well, I store raisins in there.
嗯，我在那里存放葡萄干。
For what?
为什么？
It's a healthy snack for when I'm on the go.
这是一种健康的零食，方便我随时食用。
You have any in there now?
你现在里面有吗？
I have three regulars and a golden.
有三个普通的和一个金色的。
Sometimes I like to close my eyes and surprise myself.
有时候我喜欢闭上眼睛，给自己一个惊喜。
Come on, golden.
来吧，金色的。
Yes.
是的。
Wow.
哇。
All right, my turn.
好了，轮到我了。
[exhales slowly]
（慢慢呼气）
I'm a stress-knitter.
我是个减压编织者。
A what?
什么？
When I'm stressed out, I knit.
当我感到压力大时，我会编织。
Grandma taught me and I've been doing it for years.
奶奶教我的，我已经做了好几年了。
So any time you see a sweater on the dog,
所以每当你看到狗身上有毛衣，
it came from these very nervous hands.
那就是我这双紧张的手织出来的。
You got skills, bro.
你真有本事，兄弟。
Okay, my turn.
好了，轮到我了。
[exhales heavily]
（深呼吸）
I still have an imaginary friend.
我仍然有一个想象中的朋友。
His name is DJ. He's a DJ.
他的名字是DJ，他是个DJ。
And he plays oontzing music only Dicky can hear.
他只播放迪基能听到的翁兹音乐。
That explains the headbobbing.
这就解释了为什么他会点头。
And the fist pumping.
还有挥拳。
And your math grade.
还有你的数学成绩。
Okay, Dawn, you're up.
好了，Dawn，该你了。
We all went.
我们都去了。
Okay.
好吧。
But you can't make fun of me.
但你不能取笑我。
You're safe in the circle.
你在圈子里是安全的。
[sighs] Okay.
[叹气] 好吧。
[exhaling heavily]
[沉重地呼气]
Here we go.
开始了。
You guys know Mack?
你们认识Mack吗？
I know I said I only like him as a friend,
我知道我说过我只把他当朋友，
but I think I might actually sorta like him-like him.
但我觉得我可能真的有点喜欢他了。
Wow.
哇。
That took a lot of guts.
这需要很大的勇气。
Yeah. Sure did.
是啊。确实需要。
Please let us make fun of you, please.
请让我们取笑你，拜托。
Fine. You've got five seconds.
好的，你们有五秒钟。
[singsong] all: Dawn loves Mack!
大家一起唱：Dawn喜欢Mack！
Dawn loves Mack!
Dawn喜欢Mack！
Okay. Time's up.
好了，时间到。
See?
看吧？
Our circle of trust has been restored.
我们的信任圈已经恢复了。
Hey!
嘿！
Starting now.
从现在开始。
[laughs]
（笑）
That may be the cutest little knit-hat I have ever seen.
那可能是我见过的最可爱的小针织帽。
Where did you guys get it?
你们在哪儿买的？
Pet store.
宠物店。
But it fits so perfectly.
但戴得这么合适。
Almost like it was hand-knit just for his little bird head.
简直像是专门为他那小鸟脑袋手工编织的。
It's a hat, Josie. Get over it.
乔西，那只是个帽子。别太在意。
Hey, Nicky, I'm kinda hungry.
嘿，尼基，我有点饿了。
You got any 'sins in your snack hole?
你零食袋里有啥‘罪恶’的东西吗？
Pack your own snack hole.
自己打包你的零食袋吧。
That's cold, bro.
真冷酷，兄弟。
You know I'm an outie.
你知道我是外向型的。
Best I can do is an onion ring.
我最多只能给你一个洋葱圈。
Honey, I know your clothes are for kids.
亲爱的，我知道你的衣服是给孩子穿的。
- Because they are. - But before you rule me out--
因为它们就是。但在你把我排除在外之前——
Already have. Hey, kids, come here!
已经排除了。嘿，孩子们，过来！
I need to measure you for the show.
我需要给你们量尺寸，为节目做准备。
Hey, hey, check out some of my runway skills, huh?
嘿，嘿，来看看我的走秀技巧，怎么样？
I give you Simon LeTom, because I'm...
我给你看Simon LeTom，因为我...
hungry like the wolf.
像狼一样饥饿。
[barking, howling]
[吠叫，嚎叫]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[thudding]
[重击声]
One of these days, he's actually going to be hurt.
总有一天，他真的会受伤的。
(Tom) It's today!
(汤姆) 就是今天！
Oh, oh!
哦，哦！
- Hey, Dawn. - Hey, Mack.
- 嘿，Dawn。 - 嘿，Mack。
Do you know what chapter Mr. Williams wanted us
你知道Williams先生明天要我们读哪一章吗？
to read for tomorrow?
[笑声]
[laughter]
他们在笑我们吗？
Are they laughing at us?
大家：Dawn爱Mack！Dawn爱Mack！
all: Dawn loves Mack! Dawn loves Mack!
这很有趣。
That's funny.
那挺有趣的。
My name's Mack.
我叫Mack。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, catch you later.
好吧，回头见。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Enjoying our sweaters.
享受我们的毛衣。
I feel like a sea captain!
我感觉像一个海员！
I knitted those in confidence.
我是在信任中编织的。
They're not "out-and-about" sweaters.
它们不是“外出”毛衣。
They're "relaxing at home in the circle of trust" sweaters.
这些是“在家放松，信任圈内”的毛衣。
Dude, don't worry.
伙计，别担心。
Your secret is safe.
你的秘密安全。
No one's gonna break the circle of trust.
没人会破坏信任圈。
All right, who broke the circle of trust?
好吧，谁破坏了信任圈？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
One of you little sweater-wearing snitches
你们这些穿着小毛衣的告密者之一
told my secret and now everyone in the hallway's going...
泄露了我的秘密，现在走廊里的每个人都在...
[whispers] "Dawn loves Mack." - I didn't say anything.
[低声] “Dawn喜欢Mack。” - 我什么都没说。
- Me neither. - Wasn't me.
- 我也没有。 - 不是我。
Okay. So no one's gonna admit it?
好吧，所以没人会承认？
Well, unless someone tells me...
嗯，除非有人告诉我...
You boys know what a text blast is?
你们男生知道什么是群发短信吗？
When you text on the toilet?
当你在厕所发短信的时候？
No.
不是。
It's when I text everyone in the school at the same time.
就是我同时给学校里的每个人发短信。
"Attention, everyone.
“注意了，大家。
"Nicky Harper keeps raisins in his bellybutton."
“尼基·哈珀在他的肚脐里藏了葡萄干。
- "And eats them." - [gasps]
“还吃它们。”
"Dicky Harper's best friend is a DJ..."
“迪基·哈珀最好的朋友是个DJ...”
- "And is imaginary." - [gasps]
“而且是个虚构的。”
"And Ricky Harper is a strong knotter."
“还有里基·哈珀是个打结高手。”
[gasps]
Wait, that's not that bad.
等等，这也没那么糟糕。
"Stress-knitter."
“压力编织者。”
Stupid autocorrect.
愚蠢的自动纠错。
[gasps]
Okay.
好吧。
Thumb's on send.
拇指放在发送键上。
Last chance to admit who did it.
最后一次机会承认是谁干的。
Dawn, please don't.
Dawn，请不要。
Whoever did it, fess up.
无论谁做的，坦白吧。
- It wasn't me. - Me either.
— 不是我。 — 我也不是。
All right. You made your choice.
好吧。你做出了选择。
- In 3, 2-- all: No!
— 在3，2—— 大家：不！
[phone chimes]
[手机铃声]
[phones chiming]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Dude, how 'bout knitting up
伙计，给你的兄弟织个小葡萄干袋怎么样？
a little raisin pouch for your bro?
Oontz, oontz, oontz.
咚兹，咚兹，咚兹。
What have you done?
你做了什么？
I never want to knit again.
我再也不想织东西了。
And yet I need to knit so badly.
但我又非常需要织东西。
And in case you're wondering,
如果你好奇的话，
DJ the DJ is playing a very sad song.
DJ正在播放一首非常悲伤的歌。
[sadly] Oontz...
[悲伤地]咚兹...
Oontz...
咚兹...
[choking up] Oontz.
[哽咽]咚兹。
Now you know how I feel.
现在你知道我的感受了。
What is a four-letter word for a baseball pitcher's error?
棒球投手失误的四字母单词是什么？
[squawks] Ball.
[咯咯叫] 球。
Ah, nice.
啊，不错。
Hey, the fashion show is coming together, Tom.
嘿，汤姆，时装秀正在筹备中。
This could be, like, really big for the store.
这对店铺来说可能真的很大。
Turn that "could" into "will"
把那个“可能”变成“将会”
with "America's Next Tom Model."
通过“美国下一个汤姆模特”。
Hey, Mike, will you tell Tom he's not a model?
嘿，迈克，你能告诉汤姆他不是模特吗？
[squawks] Not a model, not a model.
[咯咯叫] 不是模特，不是模特。
But I do need an emcee for the show!
但我确实需要一个时装秀的主持人！
- Mike... - [chirps]
- 迈克... - [啾啾声]
Tell her I'm in.
告诉她我参加。
[squawks] I'm in.
[尖叫] 我参加。
Excuse us, Mike.
迈克，借过一下。
Just me, right?
就我一个人吧？
Come help me get the clothing racks out of the garage.
来帮我把衣架从车库拿出来。
- Yes, I'm in. - Leave the bird.
是的，我参加。- 留下那只鸟。
Pretty lady, pretty lady.
美女，美女。
- I know that's you, Tom. - [groans]
- 我知道那是你，汤姆。- [呻吟]
Dawn, I can't believe you text blasted our secrets.
道恩，真不敢相信你把我们的秘密群发出去了。
Yeah, the whole school is laughing at us.
是的，整个学校都在嘲笑我们。
When you break the circle, you get treated like a jerkle.
当你打破圈子时，你会被当作傻瓜对待。
Mike, you would not believe my day.
迈克，你不会相信我今天经历了什么。
Thanks to one of my blabbermouth brothers,
多亏了我其中一个多嘴的兄弟，
everyone at school now knows that--
现在学校里的每个人都知道——
[singsong] Dawn loves Mack.
Dawn喜欢Mack。
Exactly!
正是！
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
[squawks] Dawn loves Mack.
Dawn喜欢Mack。
(Mike) Dawn loves Mack.
all: [singsong] Dawn loves Mack. Dawn loves Mack.
大家都说：Dawn喜欢Mack。Dawn喜欢Mack。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
And you were in the store with the kids from school.
而且你当时和学校的孩子一起在店里。
It was you! You're the blabberbeak!
原来是你！你就是那个大嘴巴！
[boys yelling in the next room]
（隔壁房间的男孩们在大声叫喊）
[groans] They're mad at me.
（叹气）他们生我的气了。
But I'll just explain it to them and they'll understand.
但我只要跟他们解释一下，他们会理解的。
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Circle of trust, she said.
她说，这是信任的圈子。
Quadfession session, she said.
她说，这是四人告解会。
And now I've dropped a stitch!
现在我漏了一针！
I can't believe this.
真不敢相信。
Now everyone's gonna think I'm weird.
现在大家都会觉得我怪怪的。
And on top of that, I'm out of raisins!
而且，我的葡萄干也没了！
- This is all Dawn's fault. - Yeah!
- 都是道恩的错。- 对！
You know what? Now that I think about it,
你知道吗？现在我想想，
maybe it's not! - Yeah!
也许不是这样！- 对！
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
Dawn's the one who brought us together.
道恩是我们能聚在一起的原因。
She's the one who tried to fix the circle of trust.
她才是那个试图修复信任圈的人。
And everything was good,
一切都很美好，
till one of you two jerkles broke it!
直到你们两个中的一个混蛋打破了它！
You mean one of you two jerkles!
你是说你们两个中的一个混蛋！
No, one of you two jerkles!
不，是你们两个中的一个混蛋！
Well, whichever jerkle broke the circle is out of the quads!
好吧，不管是哪个混蛋打破了圈子，他就不再是四人组的一员了！
[all snarling]
[所有人都咆哮着]
Yeah, I'm not so sure they'll understand.
是啊，我不确定他们会不会理解。
This is so exciting, Tom.
这太令人兴奋了，汤姆。
I am so proud of you. Break a leg.
我真为你感到骄傲。祝你好运。
You too. Ooh!
你也是。哦！
[laughs]
[笑]
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
Welcome aboard, fashion-gers.
欢迎登机，时尚达人们。
This is your pilot speaking.
这是你们的机长在讲话。
So go ahead and fashion your seat belts
请系好你们时尚的座椅安全带
because HarperArmor is about to take off!
因为HarperArmor即将起飞！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
I'm just trying to find my fashion show voice.
我只是在找我的时尚秀声音。
Now? Right before the show?
现在？就在秀前？
Up on that catwalk, I know who I am.
在T台上，我知道我是谁。
Down here, I'm just a guy with a microphone.
在这里，我只是个拿着麦克风的家伙。
Okay. Okay, okay.
好吧。好吧，好吧。
Hey, pull yourself together, Tom.
嘿，振作起来，汤姆。
[in a German accent] How about I try a German accent?
[用德国口音] 我试试德国口音怎么样？
No! No accents.
不行！不要口音。
Ugh, this is my show.
呃，这是我的秀。
Okay, Josie, two minute warning.
好的，乔西，两分钟警告。
Copy that, Mrs. Harper.
收到，哈珀女士。
Um, what's up with your brothers?
呃，你兄弟们怎么了？
[growling and grunting]
[咆哮和咕哝]
Nothing!
没什么！
Like all supermodels, they're just hungry.
就像所有超级模特一样，他们只是饿了。
I hope that's all that is,
我希望只是这样，
'cause your Mom put a lot of work into this show.
因为你们妈妈为这场秀付出了很多努力。
Hey, fellas.
嘿，伙计们。
Look what I've got.
看看我拿到了什么。
It's a circle of crust.
这是一个面包皮圈。
So let's stop fighting and start biting.
所以让我们停止打架，开始咬食吧。
- [growling] - No, no, no, no!
- [咆哮] - 不，不，不，不！
Not each other!
不是互相咬！
[Jamaican accent] Hey, mons and lady mons!
嘿，各位先生和女士们！
Dis be da debut of Anne Harper's HarperArmor!
这是Anne Harper的HarperArmor首次亮相！
Active wear for da boys and da girls.
专为男孩和女孩设计的运动装备。
- You're done, mon.
你完事了，伙计。
- Move up. They're about to start.
往前走。他们就要开始了。
Don't poke me.
别戳我。
That's not poking. This is poking.
那不算戳。这才是戳。
Oh, you want to poke.
哦，你想戳。
Hey! Why do I get poked?
嘿！为什么是我被戳？
[grunts]
哼！
- Hey, guys!
嘿，伙计们！
I thought maybe we could start all over again.
我在想，也许我们可以重新开始。
I have a quadfession to make.
我要坦白一件事。
So...look what I brought!
所以...看看我带来了什么！
Okay, so--
好吧，那么--
Great idea!
好主意！
[gong reverberates loudly]
（锣声回荡）
[laughter]
（笑声）
First up, we have Dicky Harper.
首先，我们有迪基·哈珀。
Dicky's ensemble works just as well on the field
迪基的装备在操场上和在教室里一样适用。
as it does in the classroom.
既适用于运动场，也适用于课堂。
That's classic HarperArmor versatility.
这就是HarperArmor的经典多功能性。
Next we have Ricky Harper, dressed in sporting casual wear.
接下来是Ricky Harper，穿着运动休闲装。
Ricky's ready to go from athlete to mathlete.
Ricky准备好从运动员转变为数学竞赛选手。
And since it's water resistant,
而且因为它防水，
he could also be a bath-lete.
他甚至可以成为浴室运动员。
Whatever Ricky chooses, this outfit is an A+.
无论Ricky选择什么，这套装备都是A+级的。
And now let's bring out Nicky Harper.
现在让我们请出Nicky Harper。
Ooh!
哦！
In this casual skater look,
在这套休闲滑板装扮中，
Nicky is ready to hit the halfpipe...
尼基已经准备好冲击半管了...
And not his brother.
而不是他的兄弟。
(Anne) See, folks, this is where style meets function
（安妮）瞧，各位，这就是时尚与功能的交汇点
at the HarperArmor junction.
在哈珀盔甲交汇处。
Guys, listen, I have to tell you something.
伙计们，听着，我有件事必须告诉你们。
Not now, Dawn.
现在不行，道恩。
And now, one last time, HarperArmor for him.
最后一次，为他展示哈珀盔甲。
I'm first.
我先来。
[grunting] I'm first. Trust me.
[咕哝声] 我先来。相信我。
I don't trust you.
我不信你。
I don't trust either of you.
我谁也不信。
What are they doing?
他们在干什么？
- No! - What is she doing?
- 不！ - 她在干什么？
Don't be alarmed, folks.
大家不要惊慌。
(Anne) This is just a demonstration
(安妮) 这只是为了展示
to show just how durable HarperArmor is.
哈珀装甲的耐用性。
Man, that stuff's a-durable.
天哪，那东西真耐用。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Please!
请！
Guys, please stop fighting.
伙计们，请停止争斗。
You're interrupting our triangle of hate.
你打断了我们的仇恨三角。
It's like the circle of trust,
这就像信任圈，
but it can jab you from all three sides.
但它可以从三个方向刺你。
I was the one who broke the circle of trust!
是我打破了信任圈！
You're the jerkle?
你就是那个混蛋？
Yes, I'm the jerkle.
是的，我就是那个混蛋。
all: Huh.
所有人：哼。
Get her!
抓住她！
Now what do I do?
现在我该怎么办？
All my models are gone.
我所有的模特都走了。
Not all of them.
不是全部。
You get out there and show them your sizzle.
你出去，展示你的魅力。
As you can see, HarperArmor is so versatile
如你所见，HarperArmor非常多功能
that even a grown man can fit into a boy's size medium.
即使一个成年男人也能穿上男孩的中号。
It's a small.
这是一个小号。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
So it was you who broke the circle of trust?
所以是你打破了信任的圈子？
Yes. It was me.
是的。是我。
- [squawks] It was me. It was me.
- [嘎嘎声] 是我。是我。
- Well, technically he's right.
- 嗯，从技术上讲他是对的。
Mike told everybody about Mack, but I didn't know it
迈克把马克的事告诉了所有人，但我当时并不知道
until after I text blasted your secrets.
直到我群发了你们的秘密之后
I should've trusted you. I'm sorry.
我应该相信你的，对不起
Doesn't matter. The damage is done.
没关系，伤害已经造成了
Our secrets are out there running wild.
我们的秘密现在满天飞了
Not for long.
不会太久的
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
A text blast got us into this, so...
群发短信让我们陷入这个困境，所以...
maybe one will get us out.
也许再发一次能让我们摆脱困境
[sighs]
【叹息】
"Attention, everyone...
大家注意...
"I was mad at my brothers,
我对我兄弟们很生气，
"so I made up all those things about them.
所以我编造了那些关于他们的事情。
"The only Harper secret that is true is...
唯一真实的Harper秘密是...
Yes, I do like-like Mack."
是的，我确实喜欢Mack。
Dawn, you don't have to do that.
Dawn，你不必这样做。
- Yeah, she does. - She totally does.
- 是的，她必须。 - 她绝对必须。
[phone chimes]
[手机铃声]
[phones chiming]
Oh.
哦。
[laughs] A girl likes you.
[笑] 有个女孩喜欢你。
What's that like?
那是什么感觉？
- Thanks. - Is the circle of trust repaired?
- 谢谢。 - 信任的圈子修复了吗？
All four corners.
四个角落都好了。
Good enough.
足够好了。
Now let's bring this home.
现在让我们圆满结束。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Mom, come on up. Come on, please.
妈妈，上来吧。请上来。
- Come on! - Come on, Mom!
- 快点！ - 快点，妈妈！
- And 3, 2, 1!
- 3, 2, 1！
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
- ♪
♪